MASUSU caught!!!]
I want to talk about the greatness of instrumental music.
Yay!
Yes, I'm Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume。 I'm Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume' 23.
I'm Rio Sakurai, a member of Morning Musume'23.
I'd like to invite a guest to this corner.
This time, we have a guest with us.
This time, we have a guest from Juice-Juice.
Riai Matsunaga from Juice-Juice.
Please give her a hand.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous because...
I also like to listen to instrumental music.
I often talk about this with my manager.
I was talking to my manager about how I like to listen to instrumental music, and he said, "How about you, Matsunaga? How about you, Matsunaga?
I told Sakurai immediately.
Listen, listen, I don't know if I should say this, but...
I told her that I might be able to participate in the instrumental project.
I was so happy.
I was looking forward to it.
That's right.
We don't have many opportunities to perform together.
But we do talk a lot.
It's true that I...
I often call her "Sakurai," and go over to talk to her.
I often do that.
But I thought I didn't know you well enough yet.
So you taught me a lot this time.
Oh, G, you're so beautiful!
Wait, wait, wait, I was so surprised!
Surprise, G, you're beautiful!
I showed you this.
I wanted to get to know you better, Mr. Sakurai.
May I ask you a question?
Yes, please.
Why do you like listening to instrumental music?
Well, of course I listen to the music of Coke Service.
But when I'm listening to them.
I've started to listen to the sound behind the instrumental.
I thought, "How can I make it more listenable?
I thought of instrumental music, so I started listening to instrumental music.
So you always liked instrumental music? Have you always liked instrumental music?
I think I started listening to them more after I started liking Hello.
I see.
It's not just Morning Musume.
but the Hello Project as a whole?
Yes, I listen to a lot of different groups.
That's so cool!
Did you play an instrument or something?
I've been playing the piano for about seven years.
I played piano from the age of seven to ninth grade.
Yes, I did.
Until you were 14?
Yes, until I was in the ninth grade.
Wow, why piano?
Well, I've always wanted to play an instrument.
So I asked my mother if I could learn.
I asked my mom if I wanted to learn something, and I think I ended up playing the piano.
You have musical instruments at home, but your father and mother played?
Not at all. My mom plays the violin.
That's cool.
That's right, and I told her that I wanted to learn to play an instrument.
Cool.
So you play the violin.
What's your favorite subject?
Well, I like physical education.
I didn't expect that.
Yes, I do.
Ball games.
Why?
I like to throw the ball.
I like dodgeball.
I also like basketball.
Are you good at it?
I don't know if I'm good at it, but I like it.
Do you play?
No, I don't.
That's great.
Can I ask you a question?
No! No!
Can I?
I have a favor to ask.
Well, I'd prefer if you called me Riley.
Okay, I'll do that!
Rio Sakurai, with three letters in between.
I call her Riley.
Why Riley?
I see.
Who gave it to you?
Mr. Oda.
Rio Sakurai and Rio Sakurai were both here.
So take the "Riley" out of "Rio Sakurai".
I see.
What's your favorite subject?
I'm good at P.E.
I see.
That's what you said.
Let's do an instrumental project then.So let's get to the installation project.
It's about time.
Well then, I'd like to start
I'd like to start the instrumental project.
First of all, let's start with the instrumental of Juice-Juice's
I'd like to introduce the instrumental of Juice-Juice's song
I'd like to introduce the instrumental of Juice-Juice's song.
Now it's your turn, Ms. Matsumoto.
As for me...
First of all
I'll start with this song.
Not only my body has grown up.
This song...
What does it say?
It's about a girl.
The girl
A girl
Fighting her complexes
and make something of herself.
It's a story about
There is a lyric that I like in this song.
I won't get up even if you fall down
I won't just let you get up
I love the lyrics.
It's so strong and I love it.
First of all
Let's listen to the intro of the song.
Here you go.
[ED] Yes.
Yes, that's the line now, but please remember the line "Pan-pa-pa-pan-pan" well.
Yes, I will remember it.
Now let's listen to the next one. Please subscribe to my channel!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm not the type of person who usually listens to instrumental music, but I like this part of the song when I hear it at a live performance. I'm not the type of person who usually listens to instrumental music, but I often find myself thinking, "I like this part of the song," and then I listen to it again and find that I like it.
When I'm singing the chorus...
I often find something that makes me like a song and then I listen to it again and realize I like it.
When I hear this part during a live performance, I get really excited.
I also like the way the intro melody is included in the chorus.
I'd like you to listen to this one too.
Yes, please.
After this, right?
Yes, please remember the melody line.
Now, here's the chorus. Here it is!
Enjoy the next time!
I really like this kind of thing, and I love the fact that the intro melody is included in this mitsukeru sabi, and I also love the fact that it is a part of the Morning Musume。
I also love the fact that the intro melody is included in the mitsukeru chorus. I also love the fact that the intro melody is included in the mitsukeru chorus, and that Morning Musume。
I think that song has that line not only in the chorus but also in the B melody.
I remember seeing Morning Musume。 When I was watching Morning Musume。ヌs live, I noticed that this melody was in the song all the time, and I like it.
I like 1, 2, and 3, too.
Yes!
That's for sure.
Yay!
That's how I feel. Did you get the message?
Yes, I did.
I got the message!
I got the message! Yay!
Yes, I think so. Please listen to it!
Please do!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Yes!
Yes! So I, Sakurai, would like to introduce JuiceJuice's potlit!
Yes! Potlit is the 11th single released in February 2019.
At first, I think this song has a mature tone, but the chorus and other parts of the song have a very grand orchestral sound.
I think this song starts out mature, but then it turns into a very grand orchestral style in the chorus, which I really love and it's cool.
The first point is that the number of notes in the second A-melody seems to be much larger than that of the first A-melody.
I would like you to listen to the part from the first A-melody to the B-melody first.
Please do!
This is the A melody of the first song, and although it is a rather quiet song, it has a lot of sounds in it, and the lyrics of the song also show that the first and second melodies are very similar.
I felt that the lyrics of the song changed the feeling of the main character, and I felt that the number of notes increased, so you can hear the increase in the number of notes in the second verse.
I felt that the number of notes in the lyrics had increased, so I would like you to listen to the second verse where the number of notes has increased a little. I would like you to listen to the part where the number of notes in the second verse has increased a little.
It's like the heart of a drama.
It's like the heart of a drama!
I think the rhythm has become easier to understand.
When I noticed that, I realized that the second part was even easier to ride.
This is the first point that I really liked.
The instrumental changes according to the change of mind between the lyrics of the girl in the first verse and the lyrics of the girl in the second verse.
I thought your brain is really wonderful.
Really? I'm so happy.
It's wonderful!
Well, I think it's really fun to see such thoughts come out in the instrumental.
Thank you very much.
Okay, now for the second point.
In the short 0:50 minutes, this is the part before the chorus.
You can see that the sound of the rising sound is getting faster and faster, and the accent sound after that is also getting faster and faster.
The accented sound after that is also very addictive.
I think you can feel the excitement of the chorus coming, so I would like you to listen to it.
Please listen to it.
This part is great.
The dripping sound after the chorus is also great.
I thought it was like the title of the song, "Potsuri".
I really like the way the excitement of the chorus builds up as if the chorus has arrived.
That was the second point.
It's wonderful.
The climax of the song is often heard in instrumental music, so I really like it.
It's my favorite point.
Now I would like you to listen to the end of the song at 4 minutes and 18 seconds.
This song doesn't end after the last note.
It is not the end of the song after the last note, but the end of the song suddenly and unexpectedly, as the lyrics say.
I hope you will listen to the end of the song and understand the feeling of regret.
I would like you to hear the end of the song so that you can understand that.I would like you to listen to the end where you can see that.
Please subscribe to this channel and follow me on twitter and instagram.
Please subscribe this channel and follow me on twitter and instagram.
It's amazing.
It's like it's over and done with.
I keep coming back to this song over and over again, partly because of the sadness of the ending.
It's amazing. It's true.
I feel sad now.
Yes, it did.
But it's a pretty mature and sad song.
But the chorus is very grand, and when I hear it at concerts, it gives me goosebumps in a good way.
It is a song that gives me goosebumps in a good way.
Yes, it is.
Next, I would like to introduce a song called "Mon amour" by Juice Juice.
Mon amour" means "my beloved" in French.
The title of the song "Mon amour" means "my beloved" in French, and I thought the title was very nice.
First of all, my favorite point is the introduction.
I really like the way the instruments sound together in the introduction.
I don't know, you know, the instruments are living their own lives.
I don't know how to say it, but they are living their own lives, but they are the same.
They are the same. There are so many worlds in different world lines.
But all of them are in the same time.
Let's listen to the music now. Let's listen to it now.
[ED] Here it is.
This is the part I like.
I especially like the part where the bass comes in.
Also, the guitar is stylish and cool, and I love it.
I understand. The intro part of the song really made me realize that there are a lot of instruments.
And the fact that they don't all sound the same is really impressive.
Each sound is different from the others, but the way they overlap is really wonderful.
Yes, it is. I'm glad you got the message. Thank you very much.
The second favorite point is the A melody of the second number, where the lyrics are really wonderful, and the guitar is really stylish.
And the guitar is really stylish.
So I want you to listen to that part.
Yes, please listen to it.
Here you go!
From here!
The bass guitar is cool, too.
I can tell.
The guitar line now.
I really like the "slippery" line.
I'll let you listen to it one more time, for now.
Just listen to it a little bit, paying attention to the guitar line now, the last guitar line.
Please do.
It's cool.
The guitar that comes in every once in a while is so cool and stylish.
Ah, here!
The guitar line.
It's stylish, I like it.
The rhythm of the guitar is cool.
No, it's stylish.
It's stylish.
Very stylish.
This song is very stylish.
And the next is the third pit, "Sabiskima Point.
Let's see...the drums before the chorus.
It's easier to listen to it now, so here it is.
In the beam, cool!
This place is...
It's cool, isn't it? What was that?
The line at the part where it says "toot-toot-rooong" isn't drumming at all.
It was cool. I want to hear it again. Please do.
Ever.
How did you get this?
I'm surprised to see something like this. Now.
The sound leading to the chorus is absolutely cool.
Yeah, it is. It's cool.
I really like the current drum line, too.
I found many other things I like about it.
Wow, it's so cool.
It's great.
I like strings recently, and I like the sadness of strings.
It's sad, sad, and this song is sad, too.
So, how did you like it?
The B melody is different from the A melody, of course.
The B-melody is different from the A-melody, of course, but the sound of the process to the chorus is absolutely cool in every song.
But this song stands out for its stylishness.
As Matsumoto-san said, the strings are easy to recognize.
I think that is one of the points that make it sound stylish.
What is your fourth and final favorite point?
My favorite part of this song is the bass in the chorus.
It's really, really sad.
When I first heard it, I thought the bass was crying. It's not like people are crying, it's more like the bass is squeezing you and you don't want to cry, but you do. Please listen to it.
It's here, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
You are crying.
Yes, now the bass is crying and it's so sad.
I love it.
It's really sad.
And you can hear the sound of maracas and other instruments.
I really like it.
Yes, I love it. It's like, "Yes.
Monomayor.
What did you think?
It's really stylish.
Really stylish.
It's really stylish, and the part you heard at the end is also really cool.
The accent spans after the sad string sounds are really cool, and you can hear a lot of sounds, so it's really cool.
I can hear a lot of sounds.I can hear a lot of sounds.
I like to listen to the instrumentation and look for the sounds that I really enjoy.
I also enjoy listening to the instrumentation and thinking about what these instruments are.
Thank you very much.
So, we have presented three songs by Juice-Juice.
What did you think?
I hope you will listen to the instrumental versions of the three songs I have just introduced.
Next time, we will be back with an instrumental by Morning Musume。 I would like to talk about the instrumentals of Morning Musume。
Please look forward to the next installment!
Bye bye!
Also, do you know what a home bakery is?
A home bakery?
Yes, I do.
I do a lot of home baking.
By home bakery, do you mean a machine? Or do you mean baking bread at home? What do you mean by home bakery?
You mean baking at home?
I see. What do you bake?
Raisin bread.
Raisin bread? You like raisins?
I like raisins.
Oh, really?
By yourself?
Oh, with my family.
Oh!